ab.com 2000-06-17

# Rockwell Automation - Privacy Statement

> This privacy statement explains our policy regarding any personal information you may supply to us when visiting the following Rockwell Automation web sites: 
> 
> <http://www.automation.rockwell.com/>  
>  <http://www.software.rockwell.com/>  
>  <http://www.reliance.com/>  
>  <http://www.ab.com/>
> 
> **Personal Information  
>  **There are times when we may need information from you; additionally some of our sites may require you to complete a registration form. Our goal in collecting this personal information is to offer you a more personalised browsing experience. When you let us know your preferences we will be able to deliver or allow you to access the most relevant information that meets your needs.
> 
> To extend this personalisation experience Rockwell Automation web sites may save information on your system in the form of a cookie. (For further explanation see '[cookies](http://www.automation.rockwell.com/copyright/cookies.html).').
> 
> Rockwell Automation will not share e-mail addresses with anyone outside Rockwell Automation nor disclose user information to any third party, except to our Business Partners (see Business Relationships).
> 
> This site gives you the option to remove your information from our database if you no longer wish to have this information used, as a basis for further contact with you. Please click on the following link to send your e-mail request, [opt-out@ra.rockwell.com](mailto:opt-out@ra.rockwell.com)
> 
> **Contact Us**  
>  We use e-mail links, located on the '[contact us](http://www.automation.rockwell.com/contact.html)' page to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have. This information is used to respond directly to your questions or comments. This information may be filed and used to help us prioritise our development needs and continuously improve our web sites, to meet your needs. Please check the box on the ‘contact us’ page if you want this information shared with authorized third parties.
> 
> **Business Relationships  
>  **In working with our Business Partners, we require strict contractual obligations, which ensure that your information is safeguarded. Rockwell Automation sites contain links to other Web sites. Rockwell Automation is not responsible for the privacy practices, copyright or content of such Web sites.
> 
> **Public Forums  
>  **We also make available: forums, message boards and news groups to our customers. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
